Vidya Bhayani

Navi Mumbai | 7718823702 | Vidhi.bhayani05@gmail.com

Summary

Total 12 years of experience in Accounting, Finance & Master Data Management. 9+ years of Data Management, Business Analysis, Analytics, Project Management experience. Ability to work effectively in a team environment and across all organizational levels, where flexibility, collaboration, and adaptability are important.

Education

MCOM | MUMBAI UNIVERSITY | 2013

Skills & Abilities

- Effective Communication.
- Time Management.
- Interpersonal Skills.
- Flexibility.
- Willing to learn and work hard.
- Active Participation in Team Building Activities.

Experience

DATA MANAGEMENT MANAGER | RELIANCE INDUSTRIES LTD | 06/2014 - CURRENT

- · Creation, implementation and maintenance of master data management solutions that enables user to optimize system capabilities.
- Develop process for Data Management, Integration, Governance & Quality Management for Customer
 & Vendor > Define, design & build dimensional databases to meet business requirements.
- · Develop & Monitor MDM solutions for workflows, duplication, validations of various documents, KPI.
- · Develop SOP's & monitoring SLA.
- · Assist in Application & implementation procedures of data standards & guidelines on data ownership, data replication to ensure access & integrity of data sets.
- · Identify governance process, tools or systems and work on their implementation.
- · Knowledge of various Transaction codes in SAP.
- · Data cleansing of old, unused/ duplicate data, blocking for better management & quicker access.
- Develop systems, procedures and policies for data management in an organization which ensure compliance with company standards & laws (Fiori Portal, Informatica Data Quality rules & Standard Operating Procedures)
- · Testing of Fiori in Development server & Implementing of Various data quality rules.
- Ensuring high data quality through the removal of duplicate entries and consistent classification of information and reconciliation of information against other master data systems.
- · Well versed with SAP FIORI & Supply Chain Management portal.
- Knowledge of E-Payment bank Mapping.

- Generating Various MIS reports.
- · Assisting & training Users for Authorization & Process relating to Portal.
- · Creating Videos for training Users & Making tips for the process to be followed for FIORI portal.
- · Knowledge of Sales order creation & export documentation.
- · Data Transfer to various servers.

ACCOUNTS ASSISTANT MANAGER | GAUTAM MARKETING | 05/2011 TO 05/2014

- Financial Reporting: Profit & Loss Statement, Balance Sheet, Cash Flow Statement, General Ledger & Accounting.
- Reconciliations: Monthly Bank Reconciliations.
- General Ledger: Scrutinizing Sales, Purchase, Debtors & Creditors.
- Accounts Payable & Accounts Receivable: Maintaining Books of Accounts, Checking & posting entries for Payable & Receivables.
- Query Management: Handling Customer Calls.
- Payroll Activity.
- Monthly MIS.
- Preparation of Sales Order, Purchase Entries, Daily Vouchers, Knocking off payment entries against Invoices.

Certifications

- Improving your Listening Skills, LinkedIn Learning, 2023
- Power Bi: Dashboard for Beginners, LinkedIn Learning, 2023
- High Impact Business Writing, Coursera, 2023
- Supply Chain Basics for Everyone, LinkedIn Learning, 2023
- Excel: Power Pivot for Beginners (2019), LinkedIn Learning, 2023
- Excel 2013, LinkedIn Learning, 2022
- Learning PowerPoint 2010, LinkedIn Learning, 2022
- Managing Misconduct in the Workplace, LinkedIn Learning, 2021
- Workplace Visualization, LinkedIn Learning, 2021
- Managing your Time, LinkedIn Learning, 2020
- Skills of Speaking Effectively, Alison, 2020
- Stress Management, Alison, 2020
- Google Apps: Tips, Tricks, and Techniques, LinkedIn Learning, 2020
- Google Forms Essential Training 2020, LinkedIn Learning, 2020
- Cultivating Mental Agility, LinkedIn Learning, 2020
- Pivot Table for Data Analytics, LinkedIn Learning, 2020
- Interpersonal Communication, LinkedIn Learning, 2019
- Job Skills: Supply chain & Operations, LinkedIn Learning, 2019

Languages

English, Hindi, Marathi, Gujarati.

Hobbies & Interests

Badminton & Reading Books